[Music]
lift your gaze and grace me with your
adorable fluffy cuteness for you need
not bow before me I see in you the
makings of a powerful Mage that could
stand beside the greatest in
Equestria but more importantly I see you
become something more than just great
and
[Music]
powerful I don't get it how can one
unicorn have such an edge of over
[Music]
another sometimes we have to accept that
others will grow in ways we can't
control Trixie's Journey isn't a threat
to your greatness so what does it
matter what matters is that I'm supposed
to be the
best you already are the
best in all the ways that you need to be
[Applause]
[Music]